import{c as w,b as c,d as n}from"./main.9e201f4e.js";class b{constructor(e){this.storage=e}async load(e){return this.storage.load(e)}async save(e){return this.storage.save(e)}}class l{constructor(e){this.storage=e}async load(e){return this.storage.load(e)}async save(e){return this.storage.save(e)}}function s(t){return t.title.toLowerCase().replace(/\s/g,"-")}async function i(t,e){const a=await t.createWritable();await a.write(e),await a.close()}async function d(t){const e=new FileReader;return e.readAsText(t),await new Promise(a=>{e.onload=()=>{a(e.result)}})}const f={async load(t){const{contract:e}=JSON.parse(await d(t),(a,r)=>a==="createdAt"?new Date(r):r);return w(e).updateMetadata({savedAt:new Date(t.lastModified)})},async save(t){const e=JSON.stringify({contract:t},(a,r)=>a==="savedAt"?void 0:r);if(window.showSaveFilePicker){const a=await window.showSaveFilePicker({suggestedName:s(t),startIn:"desktop",types:[{accept:{"application/json":[".json"]}}]});await i(a,e)}else await c(()=>import("./FileSaver.min.80e5b795.js").then(function(a){return a.F}),["assets/FileSaver.min.80e5b795.js","assets/vendor.6983a0d7.js"]).then(({default:a})=>{const r=new Blob([e],{type:"application/json;charset=utf-8"});a.saveAs(r,`${s(t)}.json`)})}},S={id:"db2a1d38-01fb-4ea2-bc6f-b5213413c809",title:"EVB-IT Cloud",modules:[{id:"0b141639-8718-4ad9-9839-ec89aa8a1ec4",title:"Rubrum",steps:[{id:"06817a49-dd7b-4d8a-9c5b-77702e913a30",prompt:"Schritt 1.1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{},produce:"Textbaustein: ${answer}"},{id:"c22cb3a2-2f89-47eb-b90c-a11f427ca6c8",prompt:"Schritt 1.2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"f7e2bb12-ba14-4686-8513-afbdcab276a8",prompt:"Schritt 1.3",type:"SingleChoiceAnswerStep",answer:{choices:[{text:"Auswahl A",path:[{id:"57c97b0d-4eae-439e-b747-c297b76128e5",prompt:"Schritt 1.3 A",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]},{text:"Auswahl B",path:[{id:"0b79fbb8-18f4-4824-af2a-3f4a95dc8cc6",prompt:"Schritt 1.3 B",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]}]}},{id:"f7e2bb12-ba14-4686-8513-afbdcab276a8",prompt:"Schritt 1.4",type:"MultipleChoiceAnswerStep",answer:{choices:[{text:"Auswahl 1",path:[{id:"57c97b0d-4eae-439e-b747-c297b76128e5",prompt:"Schritt 1.4 1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]},{text:"Auswahl 2",path:[{id:"0b79fbb8-18f4-4824-af2a-3f4a95dc8cc6",prompt:"Schritt 1.4 2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]}]}},{id:"5ee3e9de-5052-49ac-95ed-849df72a7167",prompt:"Schritt 1.5",type:"RichTextAnswerStep",answer:{},produce:"Textbaustein: ${answer}"},{id:"5ee3e9de-5052-49ac-95ed-849df72a7167",prompt:"Schritt 1.6",type:"RichTextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"c22cb3a2-2f89-47eb-b90c-a11f427ca6c8",prompt:"Schritt 1.7",type:"SheetAnswerStep",answer:{value:[{"Lfd Nr":"1","Produkt/ Leistung":"Amazon Web Services",Menge:"1",MVD:"Juni '22",Beginn:"01.01.22","Monatlicher Preis":"3989,86\u20AC"}]}}]},{id:"2407b57d-dfb2-487e-a4b2-d9f6f720cebe",title:"Gegenstand und Bestandteile des Vertrags",steps:[{id:"203e3a8f-e8c7-45b7-86e7-e6390393a348",prompt:"Schritt 2.1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"0b570aab-fa1b-4d93-aab3-35250b8590dc",prompt:"Schritt 2.2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"c8a04406-bba5-4968-bf2a-54122f58fbc3",prompt:"Schritt 2.3",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]},{id:"d00fdd08-805a-4c11-8e19-c57ca770f09f",title:"Gegenstand der Leistungen",steps:[{id:"28acb64b-2c87-44c2-a112-10128a1ca546",prompt:"Schritt 3.1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"3f460bf7-305f-4d53-a01b-074aa148c179",prompt:"Schritt 3.2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"3cd87b83-60fa-4fd3-953b-fb0ad6d57a46",prompt:"Schritt 3.3",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"253a3dcf-9731-4537-8be3-908ec0e0c887",prompt:"Schritt 3.4",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]}]},p={findById(t){const e=localStorage.getItem(t);if(e===null)throw new Error("Playbook not found");const{playbook:a}=JSON.parse(e,(r,o)=>["createdAt","savedAt"].includes(r)?new Date(o):o);return n(a)},save(t){localStorage.setItem(t.id,JSON.stringify({playbook:t}))}},h=n(S).updateMetadata({createdAt:new Date});p.save(h);const u={async load(t){const{playbook:e}=JSON.parse(await d(t),(a,r)=>a==="createdAt"?new Date(r):r);return n(e).updateMetadata({savedAt:new Date(t.lastModified)})},async save(t){const e=JSON.stringify({playbook:t},(a,r)=>a==="savedAt"?void 0:r);if(window.showSaveFilePicker){const a=await window.showSaveFilePicker({suggestedName:s(t),startIn:"desktop",types:[{accept:{"application/json":[".json"]}}]});await i(a,e)}else await c(()=>import("./FileSaver.min.80e5b795.js").then(function(a){return a.F}),["assets/FileSaver.min.80e5b795.js","assets/vendor.6983a0d7.js"]).then(({default:a})=>{const r=new Blob([e],{type:"application/json;charset=utf-8"});a.saveAs(r,`${s(t)}.json`)})}},A=()=>p,m=()=>new b(f),g=()=>new l(u);export{A as a,g as b,m};
